Mitchell George

mitchgeorge8@gmail.com | (419) 631-6268 | Columbus, OH | www.linkedin.com/in/mitchell-g-george

SUMMARY

Engineer with a B.S. in Electrical Engineering, full stack web development certification, and 4+ years of experience working with a team. Looking to apply analytical skills and close attention to detail in a full-time Developer role.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Nifco America – Customer Quality Engineer

2021 - Present

Handling part quality complaints from a wide range of Nifco's customers. Working with cross-functional teams to establish root causes and implement permanent corrective actions.

Nifco America - Quality Engineering Intern

2019

Built data analytics tools that improved data usage and clarity to increase customer responsiveness. Included automated reports and spreadsheets that are used daily across the department.

Stoneridge, Inc. – *Engineering Intern (multiple)*

2017, 2018

Tracked and analyzed production scrap on two high volume lines. Designed various machine improvements, conducted tests, and monitored machine performance.

EDUCATION

7/2022	Coding Boot Camp
	The Ohio State University
4/2021	Bachelor of Science, Electrical Engineering
	Mount Vernon Nazarene University
5/2017	Associate of Applied Science, Industrial Technology
	North Central State College

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Mount Vernon Nazarene University - Resident Assistant

2018-2021

Worked with a team to enforce campus policies, plan student events, and foster a healthy community. Oversaw a dorm/apartment of students who reported to me whenever there were issues.

ACTIVITIES

Honors Program, 2017–2020 Small group leader, 2018–2021 Leader of the Sustainability Club, 2020–2021 Student mentor, 2019 **SKILLS**

Autodesk applications
Microsoft Office
Data analysis
Dprinting

Communication
Organization
Problem Solving
Adaptability